[{"id":"lv9mdkpc","question":"Böbrek yetmezliği hangi organ kaynaklıdır?","answerOptions":["Liver","Heart","Kidney","Stomach"],"answer":"Kidney","type":"multiple choice","hardness":"medium","marksWorth":1,"lockedQuestion":"Turkish","lockedAnswer":"English"},{"id":"lv9mdilb","question":"In which section can piston problems occur on a ship?","answerOptions":["Motor","Armada","Pupa","Currency"],"answer":"Motor","type":"multiple choice","hardness":"medium","marksWorth":1,"lockedQuestion":"English","lockedAnswer":"English"},{"id":"lv9mdpau","question":"Скільки часу людина може прожити без води?","answerOptions":[""],"answer":"3 дні","type":"fill in the blank","hardness":"easy","marksWorth":1,"lockedQuestion":"Ukrainian","lockedAnswer":"Ukrainian"},{"id":"lv9mdm0d","question":"How many types of kidney failure are there?","answerOptions":["1","2","3","4"],"answer":"2","type":"multiple choice","hardness":"hard","marksWorth":1,"lockedQuestion":"English","lockedAnswer":"English"},{"id":"lv9mdktr","question":"How to solve piston problems on a ship?","answerOptions":["Repair","Change","Buffer","Living"],"answer":"Change","type":"multiple choice","hardness":"hard","marksWorth":1,"lockedQuestion":"English","lockedAnswer":"English"},{"id":"lv9mdmlo","question":"In which condition can kidney failure occur?","answerOptions":[],"answer":"High blood pressure","type":"fill in the blank","hardness":"easy","marksWorth":1,"lockedQuestion":"English","lockedAnswer":"English"},{"id":"lv9mdo5r","question":"Болезнь почек невозможно излечить.","answerOptions":["True","False"],"answer":"Wrong","type":"true and false","hardness":"medium","marksWorth":1,"lockedQuestion":"Russian","lockedAnswer":"English"},{"id":"lv9mdp1k","question":"На каждом корабле возникают проблемы с поршнями.","answerOptions":["Верно","Неправильно"],"answer":"Неправильно","type":"true and false","hardness":"easy","marksWorth":1,"lockedQuestion":"Russian","lockedAnswer":"Russian"}]